[Music]
hi and welcome I'm honey and over
September 2018 but particularly in the
Halloween terror October event there's a
whole bunch of new over two interactions
wives aren't wrong about Widowmaker
interesting Brigid turned Farah now
apparently best buds there's musings on
the past between Genji and McCree lucio
trying to use Genji as disco lights and
a whole lot more time codes are in the
description below if you just want to
skip listen to the interactions I'm
going to comment only selectively on a
few my favorites the new Junkin Stein
interactions in the event I'll get them
here on the channel as soon as I can
the old ones from previous years are in
the description and placed here as well
okay let's get stuck in so Brigitta has
a whole bunch of interactions they're
both children of over watches original
founding members so it looks as though
the two have a lot in common including
going to the gym I'm really looking
forward to fighting with you Farah we
overwatch brats have to stick together
Brigitta I'd love it if you could take a
look at my armor sometime it'll take
some time for me to get familiar with
the design but if you don't mind I'd
love to did you ever want to join
overwatch growing up not after how they
treated Reinhard he deserved better
hey Brigitta want to go hit the weights
only if we can get something to eat
afterwards it's true you have been
slacking off a bit lately I've stitched
you up so many times it's a wonder you
can still fight some bumps and bruises
nothing to worry yourself about now
there's an interesting line between
Brigitta and Sombra and summarize
another line as well I wonder what
summer knows about why Reinhardt left
overwatch does she sound sympathetic or
not I'd love to hear your thoughts you
know I've seen Reinhardt's overwatch
file what are you getting at I wonder if
he's really told you the truth about his
retirement what is the truth behind her
own hunts retirement well with all of
those briquette when fire aligns fara
has a couple of new lines she has a chat
with doom fist actually references her
comic mission statement as well in a
line with zenyatta and talks about her
plans to go and see her dad which is
very nice like the old reflections
Christmas comic a lot of good people in
helix died when you escaped people I
knew
don't make it personal it had nothing to
do with you
furry huh any plans for the winter I'm
flying home to see my dad I'm going to
head to Canada to see
my dad and uh Nick in my squad took his
own life rather than be controlled by an
AI a noble but tragic sacrifice I hope
that you will honor it there's a bit of
a trend we have characters who are
getting reworks also getting new
interactions probably voice line
recording at the same time so Taub has a
whole bunch filling in some lines that
were single parts with Reinhardt as well
as a few other bits and bobs as well who
need to stop telling those ridiculous
stories Reinhardt
no one believes they're real isn't it
enough to be an engineer
Brigitta I felt like I had to do more
why does everyone keep pestering me
about my yard Vox Angela you should know
that no one could stop Brigitta from
doing something she had her mind set on
she's a lean home after all
wonder what massive Centrepointe I paid
for that yet
whoever built your mech did a good job
none of that AI mess well if you want to
give me some upgrades I'm all ears
ken gene McCrae also have a few slightly
pensive lines with various different
characters do not blame yourself for
mourned dad that's death it was not your
fault
you don't understand Genji I could have
saved him maybe the world would have
been better off if it had been me
instead of him Genji yeah how did you
ever get used to you know and it was
hard enough for me there was just the
one arm it was that long and a difficult
road but now I feel at ease in my own
body I do not fear death
no you finally living the challenge how
about I hook up your lights to my music
that is not what they're for I'm not
100% sure this is right but it seems
like Genji might even give in just this
one time and this has to be on Route 66
between the two why have you come back
to this place McCree the only thing it
ever is
unfinished business and unhappy history
just remember for we ain't playing with
toy guns anymore
good I'm much better with the real thing
what's your Halloween costume gonna be
this year for cold mercy Oh sir gets a
couple of updates Tracy you should be
careful we don't know the side effects
of using the chronal accelerator
considering the alternatives I'm willing
to take the risks zenyatta I must admit
I don't understand how your healing
works and I do not understand much of
how you heal dr. Ziegler I suppose we
must all take some things on faith Maura
has some brilliant lines including this
one which I can't find a pair for
there's just her eloquence and her
intelligence personified also
interactions as well I love this line so
much the struggle for Marshall
superiority is so tedious the
superiority of ideas that is the coin of
my realm look at this world Symetra see
what science has wrought of course
science obeys the laws of nature it is
only to be expected started any wars
lately I'd have to check my schedule
your state of chronal uncertainty is
fascinating to me tracer I do wish you'd
allow me to study you well I'm truly
touched by your offer
haha I think I'll have to pass much more
talkative now aren't you Genji I find
the company more agreeable these days
sunyata Symetra and tracer have also
been in the studio recording a few more
lines here's a few interactions between
the three and then we'll go on to a
really interesting one between honor and
Widowmaker what can you know of life
only that which I have observed
experienced and processed all is one
within the iris Sumitra I am familiar
with your work
I look forward to seeing it in person
should I be worried
I heard you leveled skyscrapers I
thought I'd taken care of you you're
more resilient than you look I've come
back from worse does it bother you
knowing that you could have saved the
one that has life we are all responsible
for the choices we've made now how about
this one between honour and Widow it
seems I was wrong about you Emily
ah oh why am I here huge unanswered
question why was on a wrong what she's
seen what's happened that has caused her
to think that she was wrong about Emily
as she discovered what's happened to her
that's a really really interesting one
to me story wise honor also has some
corny interactions with Jim fist and
hands oh why did you abandon the
assassins art
I never was an assassin I killed only
because it was necessary I know Amaury I
hate to see your talents wasted now
there is this line in the voice lines
but I don't think it's the pair to the
team face when I don't think I'd be this
cordial to the investor what do you
think that's the story of my life
Sombra also has a few new lines she
knows everything about the overwatch
characters I think we need her to be
feeling into the law nowadays what
interesting things I've learned about
your employers
miss vaswani what have you heard hey
Sombra I hear you're a master of
unlocking what are you talking about
it's a reference to the tribe coming
from resident evil in terms of the
unlocking of doors and videogames in the
fact that I'm looking into is this
massive skill that only certain people
with loads of expertise can actually do
now hamon doesn't have many interactions
but what wrecking ball interaction is
there are I would Sombra so here are
those examples now I've seen it all I'm
supposed to work with a giant rat they
don't pay me enough for this you remind
me of my stuffed bear arturito I like
him better and he may have seen the a
demon hunter swampers can go live now
this is with the Blizzcon Virtual Ticket
if you're watching this in October 2018
I have a giveaway that I'm going to be
launching for this details will be in
the description below and have a listen
to these lines because there might be a
way if you remember something here you
get a little bonus I'm on the hunt Hale
sweet revenge do you want more don't
make me laugh bleed you filth you won't
survive that that's it
and last but not least some more single
interactions that will probably get PES
for them later when recordings are done
and some map interactions as any art or
Torbjorn brigita a lot of people have
new interactions on maps particularly
with it seems junk town and I should've
alder so those will be at the end I am
NOT the Easter Bunny your body seems to
be adapting well to the changes Gabriel
time is a river it may be stopped for a
while but it will all
is flow the same direction do we have
time to go on some rides flight to dusk
what is my favorite I think I'm gonna
get tetanus just from looking at this
place don't think we'll be taking a
family vacation here anytime soon
Papa might have a breakdown the quality
of the craftsmanship here hurts my soul
how in the world does this place even
work it is sad to see a place that might
have known peace reduce to this I feel
most unwelcome here during green my
brother's dream but not to me thanks
much achayan if you like this video like
subscribe comment do let me know what
you think what your favorite
interactions are in the comments below
sorry my channel has been quiet for a
while I'll do an update video and talk
about that in a bit but it's cons coming
up I am always going to be the overwatch
little interaction some voice lines here
the videos you loved at most for the
past two years because thanks to my
patrons on patreon who make this place
possible as do you guys and everyone who
supports Cheers cheating in I've been
hammy take it easy